[{"answer": "Because when you were on this other show you were (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Why have you given me the big exclusive interview?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "I'm outraged.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I heard Monday, early afternoon.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "When did you hear that Nathan had been killed?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Disbelief, I think, because there's so many mistakes.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Let me ask you, Bernadette, as Katie's mother and as the grandmother of these poor young girls now who have no father, what is your reaction as you found out more and more about the background here?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I think that they need to be more cautious and I guess look into who purchase these guns.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Do you have a view about gun control, about background checks, about any of those things that have been so heatedly discussed in America?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I haven't went into detail.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Have you been able to explain it at all?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I don't want Dr. Murray to answer that question.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Can you answer that question?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Can I ask you, do you know -- I mean, do you know the answer to that question?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question in my mind, Piers, that the concert promoter employed Conrad Murray.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Who was employing Conrad Murray to be a practitioner for Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Well, not all of it.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "It all comes down to him, doesn't it, in the end?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "These are people working for AEG, working for him, working for the show.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "These are people working for AEG?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Could be very significant.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How significant will any of that be when this trial starts?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I really don't.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Do you think there's any truth in that?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "But when you hear Conrad Murray behave like that, that's not the behavior of, as he would pitch himself to us, being a decent, honorable, straightforward physician, is it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "She and the children are going to win, in my opinion.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Is she going to win, Katherine Jackson on behalf of the family?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, I think first, you look at the recommendations.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Who are these school employees who are going to be trusted with being the great defenders against shooters?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Well, I can't speak for Mr. LaPierre, but let me say this about Asa Hutchinson.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Is he -- does he say that schools are gun- free zones or not?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Oh, no, wait a second, to fight the background checks, which is where America's come, which is where I told you America would come the last time I was on your program.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "He's not in the gun business?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it's politics and people want to blame the Republicans.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Why are we not having this done in Washington?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "September 2014.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "And Jay's existing contract, I think, ends in probably September of 2014?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Let's listen to a bit of this lovely duet last night between these two guys.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How long do you want it to go on?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "No, I don't think it is at all.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Ken, are we buying all this bonhomie between everybody over there now, that it's all one big happy family and the transition has been agreed?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Well, they decided not to do it when Conan was available.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Could he do that, do you think?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "If I were Jay, I would take my dignity and leave quietly and count my millions.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Ken, would you go to Fox if you were Jay if you were offered it?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Bubba, how the devil are you?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "No, it's April 2nd.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Now, is this hovercraft true or is it just an April Fool gag?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Hopefully he gets sick.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "How are you going to beat him?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "First you've got to look at the adoption.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "How's it changed your life in the last year?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Yes, you know -- yes, I do.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Any other deeply intimate, personal questions you want to get off your chest (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "No, it's just because you are that (ph).", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Is it because I'm British?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Well, it's not really -- it's not you inviting me back.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "What is the point of me interviewing you if all you're going to do is call me that?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "No, I don't think anybody should like being a celebrity.", "docId": "130402pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Do you like the celebrity aspect of what you've become since winning the Masters?", "qSentId": 689}]